Finding Aid for Helen Hornbeck Tanner papers, 1930s-2009
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Helen Hornbeck Tanner papers 1930s-2009
Tanner, Helen Hornbeck
14 linear feet
8679 Aa 2
Historian of American Indian history and literature, research associate at the Newberry Library, secretary of the Michigan Commission on Indian Affairs, and expert witness in legal cases involving Indian treaty rights. The collection contains correspondence, reports, clippings, and printed material concerning work of the Commission and status of Indians in Michigan; also depositions and other documents in the case of United States v. Michigan, landmark Indian fishing rights case.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection was the gift of Helen Hornbeck Tanner (donor no. 4308 ) and came to the library in multiple accessions. The last accession came from the Tanner estate through Helen Tanner’s daughters.
No further additions to the records are expected.
The collection is open to research.
Helen Hornbeck Tanner was a distinguished scholar of American Indian history and literature, publishing books on the Caddo and the Ojibwa as well as on early eighteenth-century Spanish Florida.
A native of Minnesota, born July 5, 1916, Helen Hornbeck Tanner grew up mainly in Kalamazoo, Michigan. She was educated at Swarthmore College in Pennsylvania (1937); University of Florida, Gainesville (1948); and the University of Michigan, where she received a doctoral degree in 1961. She taught courses in Latin American history, and later in American Indian history for the University of Michigan Extension Service and occasionally at the U-M Ann Arbor campus.
Beginning in 1963, she began a career as an expert witness in cases heard by the Indian Claims Commission in Washington D.C. Probably her most significant single case was United States v. Michigan, which established Native American fishing rights in the Great Lakes based on 19th-century treaties. Tanner was the lead witness for the plaintiffs and summarized the evidence of early and continuing Native American fishing on the lakes. From 1966 to 1970 she was a member of the Michigan Commission on Indian Affairs.
Her Bibliography of the Ojibwa (1974) was one of the early publications of the Center for American Indian History at The Newberry Library. She also prepared maps of Indian locations for the Atlas of Early American History (1976), and consulted for the Smith Center for the History of Cartography in 1974. In 1976, she joined the Newberry staff as director of the project that produced the Atlas of Great Lakes Indian History (1987). She remained as a Research Associate, and in 1996 she became a Senior Research Fellow.
She died June 15, 2011.
The Helen Hornbeck Tanner papers are composed of ten series: Personal / Biographical; Correspondence; Articles and other writings; Research and Writing Projects; Conferences and symposia; Topical files; Michigan Commission on Indian Affairs; U.S. v. Michigan; Other Litigation; and Printed Material.
Subjects:
Fishing--Great Lakes (North America); Indians of North America--Michigan.; Caddo Indians.; Keewaydinoquay.; Michigan Commission on Indian Affairs.
Genre:
Photographs.
- Personal / Biographical
  The Personal / Biographical series is of most value for the transcripts of oral history interviews that Tanner gave to researchers about her life and career activities.
  - Biographical information, vita, etc. (Box 1)
  - Clippings and tear sheets of articles about HHT, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Frances C. Allen Alumni Reception for Helen Tanner July 12, 2003 (Box 1)
  - Transcripts of interviews with HHT conducted by James Bennett 1990 (Box 1)
  - Transcripts of interviews with HHT conducted by Ivor Miller 2004, 2006 (Box 1)
  - Wilson Tanner and Tanner Award (psychology award in Wilson Tanner's honor) (Box 1)
  - Family miscellaneous (Box 1)
  - Photographs (Box 1)
- Correspondence
  The Correspondence series dates from the 1930s to 2009. The letters are from students, colleagues and other historians, publishers, Native American activists and community leaders, and from attorneys and others involved in litigation involving Indian rights. The researcher should note that there is correspondence throughout the collection.
  - Undated (Box 1)
  - 1930s (Box 1)
  - 1950s (Box 1)
  - 1960s (Box 1)
  - 1970 (Box 1)
  - 1971 (Box 1)
  - 1972 (Box 1)
  - 1973 (Box 1)
  - 1974 (Box 1)
  - 1976 (Box 1)
  - 1977 (Box 1)
  - 1978 (Box 1)
  - 1979 (Box 1)
  - 1980 (Box 1)
  - 1981 (Box 1)
  - 1982 (Box 1)
  - 1983-1984 (Box 1)
  - 1985 (Box 1)
  - 1986 (Box 1)
  - 1987 (Box 1)
  - 1988 (Box 1)
  - 1989 (Box 1)
  - 1990 (Box 1)
  - 1991 (Box 1)
  - 1992 (Box 1)
  - 1993 (Box 1)
  - 1994 (Box 1)
  - 1995 (Box 1)
  - 1996 (Box 1)
  - 1997 (Box 1)
  - 1998 (Box 1)
  - 1999 (Box 2)
  - 2000 (Box 2)
  - 2001 (Box 2)
  - 2002 (Box 2)
  - 2002 Christmas (Box 2)
  - 2003 (Box 2)
  - 2004 (Box 2)
  - 2005 (Box 2)
  - 2006 (Box 2)
  - 2006-2008 (Box 2)
  - 2009 (Box 2)
- Articles and other writings
  The Articles and other writings series contains drafts of articles, reprints, books reviews written by her, and reviews of her own work.
  - Early School Writings (Box 2)
  - Undated, The Indian Division of the Civilian Conservation Corp: The Indian New Deal (Box 2)
  - Undated, The Delaney Murder Case (Box 2)
  - Undated, Treaties (for the Chicago Encyclopedia) (Box 2)
  - 1950, Tanner Seminar Papers (Box 2)
  - 1975, Gainesville Sun (Box 2)
  - 1976, Communications Network of the Spanish Borderlands (Box 2)
  - 1978, The Glaize in 1792; A Composite Indian Community (paper given at the 1977 meeting of the American Society for Ethnohistory) (Box 2)
  - 1979, Coocoochee: Mohawk Medicine Woman (Box 2)
  - 1980, The Land and Water Communications System of the Southeastern Indians (Box 2)
  - 1981, Cucuchi: Curandera (chapter from book Struggle & Survival in Colonial America) (Box 2)
  - 1983, "Caddo Survival on an International Frontier" (Box 2)
  - 1987 Statement of HHT appearing before the Subcommittee on Interior and Related Agencies of the House Committee on Appropriations and speaking on behalf of appropriations for the National Endowment for the Humanities (Box 2)
  - 1990, Chippewa Death March: Explaining the Extremes in Old Northwest Indian Removal (Box 2)
  - 1990, Where are the Ojibwas? -- The Challenge of Regional Terminology, presented at 22nd Algonquian Conference, Chicago, October 27, 1990 (Box 2)
  - 1991, The Ojibwa (various drafts), 3 folders (Box 2)
  - 1993, The Ojibwa-Jesuit Debate at Walpole Island, 1844 (Box 2)
  - 1993, La Pointe, Lac Courte Oreilles, and the Ojibwa Perspective, The Newberry Library, Chicago (Box 2)
  - 1994, American National Biography -- biographical sketches written
    - Vicente Manuel de Zéspedes y Velasco (Box 2)
    - Henry Rowe Schoolcraft (Box 2)
  - 1998, History vs. The Law: Processing Indians in the American Legal System (reprint of speech given in 1998 at the University of Detroit Mercy Law School at the dedication of the School's Indian Law Center) (Box 2)
  - 1999, In the Fields of French Colonial History in Illinois (Box 2)
  - 2002, Indians of Betsie Bay and the Surrounding Country (Box 2)
  - 2004, Mapping the Grand Traverse Indian Country: The Contributions of Peter Dougherty (Box 2)
  - 1999-2004, Miscellaneous articles (Box 2)
  - Walpole Island paper, correspondence and resource material (Box 3)
  - Writings unidentified and fragmentary (Box 3)
  - HHT reviews of the papers and writings of others (Box 3)
  - Book Reviews written by HHT (Box 3)
  - Reviews of HHT books (Box 3)
- Research and Writing Projects
  The Research and Writing Projects series documents both proposed and completed research and writing endeavors. Much of this concerns her highly praised Atlas of Great Lakes Indian History.
  - Atlas of Great Lakes Indian History (formerly The Settling of North America)
    - Correspondence and topical files, 14 folders (Box 3)
      (include Bernard Bailyn correspondence)
  - T. Law Production. "The Ancient Ones" 1993-1994 (Box 3)
  - Newberry Library. "Atlas of Early American History" 1974-1975 (Box 3)
  - Great Lake Documentary Project 2004 (Box 3)
  - Houghton Mifflin. "Encyclopedia of the American Indian" 1994-1996 (Box 3)
  - Reader's Digest. "Through Indian Eyes" 1993-1996 (Box 3)
  - Reader's Digest Atlas. Native Americans at Time of European Contact, c 1500 AD 1997-1998 (Box 3)
  - Time-Life. People of the Lakes 1994 (Box 3)
  - Great Lakes Film Project 1994 (Box 3)
  - "Brazil -- Beyond the Rain Forest" 1995 (Box 3)
- Conferences and symposia
  The Conferences and symposia series detail those conferences at which Helen Tanner was a speaker. Beside conferences on Native history, there is also a file on the First International Conference on The Future of Indigenous Peoples held in May 2000.
  - American Society for Ethnohistory October, 1971 (Box 4)
  - University of Michigan Center for Continuing Education of Women 1973 (Box 4)
  - Newberry Library Conference on the American Indian and the American Revolution February 1975 (Box 4)
  - American Historical Association 1976 (Box 4)
  - Saint Augustine Historical Society April 1988 (Box 4)
  - Twenty Second Algonquian Conference October 1990 (Box 4)
  - Enduring Peoples of America conference, Western Michigan University March 1992 (Box 4)
    (include HHT paper Michigan Indians in the Center of Great Lakes History)
  - Culture and Colonization in North America colloquium 1992 (Box 4)
  - Native Americans and the Republic symposium 1992 (Box 4)
    (Star of Republic Museum)
  - The Woodlands Indians symposium July 1994 (Box 4)
  - American Society for Ethnohistory 1997 (Box 4)
    (include HHT paper "Caddo Status and Influence Between the Mississippi River and the Rio Grande, 1200-1830A.D.)
  - Siouan and Caddoan Languages Conference May 1998 (Box 4)
  - Native American Treaty Rights Training session June 1999 (Box 4)
  - First International Conference on The Future of Indigenous Peoples May 2000 (Box 4)
  - State Bar of Michigan, American Indian Law Section September 2001 (Box 4)
  - Sauder Village lecture 2003 (Box 4)
  - "The Healing Legacies of Eastern Cuba: Ancient Knowledge and Contemporary People," 2003 (Box 4)
  - "Dialogues about Indigenous Histories and Indigenous Futures," University of British Columbia 2005 (Box 4)
  - Lectures and conferences miscellaneous (Box 4)
- Topical files
  The Topical files series, arranged alphabetically, consists of subject correspondence, papers and letters from named individuals, collected materials relating to specific interests and activities, research material. Of interest is her correspondence with, and articles written by Native American writer and personality Keewaydinoquay M. Peschel (called Kee by those who knew her). Kee was an Indian medicine woman, educated at Central Michigan University and Michigan State University in botany and biology. She lived on Garden Island, one of the Beaver Islands in Michigan. Tanner and Tanner corresponded with each other over many years.
  - American Association of University Women, correspondence 1958-1971 (Box 4)
  - Bay Mills Indian Community 1996-1997 (Box 4)
  - Becker, Mary Druke, letters and reprints of her articles 2003 (Box 4)
  - Bell, Robert C., Jr. attorney, letters with Bell and David Lewis regarding appraisal of Indian land 1963-1964, 1970 (Box 4)
  - Beulah Library / Benzie County Historical Society 2005-2007 (Box 4)
  - Blue Jacket and Van Swearingen (Box 4)
    (regarding research into question whether Blue Jacket was white captive Marmaduke Swearingen)
  - Buell (Abel Buell 1784 Map), letters and other material relating to use of map in exhibit designed for American Revolution Bicentennial Administration 1974-1975 (Box 4)
  - Burt Lake Band of Ottawa and Chippewa Indians 1996-2000 (Box 4)
  - Caddo Indians
    - Archaeological sites, Oklahoma. Correspondence 1970-1972 (Box 4)
    - Grants
      - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation grant application to a history of the Caddo (Box 4)
      - American Council of Learned Societies. HHT grant proposal to write a history of the Caddo People of the Red River Frontier 1989-1992 (Box 4)
      - National Endowment for the Humanities. HHT grant proposal to write a history of the Caddo People of the Red River Frontier 1989-1992 (Box 4)
    - Conferences
      - Caddo Conference (conference papers and related) 1991 (Box 4)
      - Caddo Conference (notes and related) 1995 (Box 4)
      - Caddo History and Ethnology Symposium 1999 (Box 4)
        (include HHT paper, "Tumultuous Decade: The Caddo Treaty of 1835 and the Aftermath")
      - Caddo Conference 2001 (Box 4)
      - Caddo conferences (miscellaneous) (Box 4)
    - Caddo History, correspondence about 1989-1990 (Box 4)
    - Jelk, E.B. HHT review of his article on the Caddo Indians (Box 4)
    - Magnaghi, Russell, letters 1972 (Box 4)
    - Newkumet, Phil. Letters and collected materials (Box 4)
    - Research and source notes (Box 4)
    - University of Oklahoma Press. HHT proposal to publish her history of the Caddo People of the Red River Frontier and other projects 1990, 1996 (Box 4)
  - Cartography, letters about, with G. Malcolm Lewis and the Hermon Dunlap Smith Center for the History of Cartography 1975-1976 (Box 4)
  - Champoux, Isidore, letters regarding his estate (Box 4)
  - Chippewa -- Sault Ste. Marie Tribe
    - General (Box 5)
    - Report by Frederic Hatch entitled "Residual Interests in the Title to the Methodist Mission Reserve Held by the Sault Ste. Marie Tribe of Chippewa Indians: a partial report" January 1978 (Box 5)
  - Chippewa -- Saginaw Chippewa Tribe of Michigan (brochure and research papers) (Box 5)
  - Chippewa -- Wisconsin spear fishing (Box 5)
  - Coolfont Resort (Sam Ashelman), clippings and letters 1995-1996 (Box 5)
  - Cuba, letters and other materials concerning in part HHT's work in preparing a course on the Cuban Revolution intended as one unit in a course taught by James A. Leith, Queen's University, Kingston, Ontario 1971-1973, 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Dougherty, Peter, Transcript of his diary (1838-1840) (from Ruth Craker, papers, Leelanau Museum) (Box 5)
  - Eastern Michigan University and the use of Huron name for its athletic teams 1991 (Box 5)
  - Endreson, Douglas, attorney, regarding cultural resources management plan prepared for the Crandon Nuning Company, Crandon, Wisconsin 2001 (Box 5)
  - Ethnohistorical Report on the Little River Band Ottawa Indians. Report of Richard White and James McClurken 1994 (Box 5)
  - Ethridge, Robbie, papers with HHT commenting on her work 2001 (Box 5)
  - Garland Publishing, including letters from David Horr commenting on the firm's American Indian Ethnohistory Series 1973-1974 (Box 5)
  - Gronda, Steve. Letters and other materials (Box 5)
  - Hickerson, Nancy (Polly), letters to HHT with copies of her writings 1987-1992 (Box 5)
  - Hyde, George E., photocopy of manuscript with HHT notes and comments (Box 5)
  - Indian Claims Commission -- correspondence with attorneys Rodney J. Edwards and James R. Fitzharris and various other Commission documents 1969-1971 (Box 5)
  - Keewaydinoquay M. Peschel ("Kee")
    - Biographical information: clippings, vita, notes, University of Michigan records (Box 5)
    - Correspondence 1976-1980, undated, 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Geniusz, Wendy and Mary -- proposed biography of Kee (Box 5)
    - Life Story Committee 2003 (Box 5)
    - Michigan Humanities Council -- "Planning Grant for the Writing and Dissemination of the Life Story of Keewaydinoquay -- Woman Between Worlds" 2001-2002 (Box 5)
    - Miniss Kitigan Drum -- newsletter and grant material 1979-1987 (Box 5)
    - Writings
      - Kinnic Kinnick "Gift of Bear" ( 1977 ) (Box 5)
      - Min: Anishnaubeg Ki Nitawiiagiminan ( 1978 ) (Box 5)
      - Direction We Know: Walk in Honor ( 1979 ) (Box 5)
      - The Girl Who Was Raised By The Owls ( 1984 ) (Box 5)
      - Sisters of the Moon Shields and the Eighteen Canoes ( 1995 ) (Box 5)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 5)
  - Keller, Mark, letters and papers "The Canal Lands of Keweenaw Bay" ( 1984 ) and "The Chippewa Land of Keweenaw Bay" ( 1981 ) (Box 6)
  - King, Cecil (professor at Queen's University, Kingston, Ont.), appraisal of scholarly work by HHT 1992-1993 (Box 6)
  - Kohler and Black, attorneys, correspondence and legal documents regarding case of Grand Traverse Band of Ottawa and Chippewa Indians case involving fishing rights 1999-2000 (Box 6)
  - LaFrance, Joseph, HHT paper and research material 1993-1994 (Box 6)
  - Latin America trip 1994, Vera Cruz (Box 6)
  - Latin America trip 1994-1995, Cuba, Brazil, Mexico (Box 6)
  - Leonard, Irving A., letters 1954, 1969 (Box 6)
  - Little Traverse Bay Bands of Odawa Indians 1996-1997, 2 folders (Box 6)
    (include HHT consulting contract)
  - McKay, Lawrence (city of Frankfort Attorney), correspondence and other material concerning Native American rights in Betsie Bay 2001-2002 (Box 6)
  - Maloney, Walter H., attorney, letters 1963-1964 (Box 6)
  - Malouf, Dick, letter and enclosure relating to the Quapaw Tribe 1971 (Box 6)
  - Mt. Pleasant Indian Industrial School, brief history 1983 (Box 6)
  - Michigan Commission on Indian Affairs 1966-1971 (Box 6)
  - Michigan History Commission 1973-1975 (Box 6)
  - Milwaukee Public Museum, Nancy Lurie 1990-1991 (Box 6)
  - Minnetrista Council for Great Lakes Native American Studies 1992-1994 (Box 6)
    (includes HHT's paper "The Ohio Valley's Indian Network")
  - Nas'naga, letter and book of poetry 2000 (Box 6)
  - Newberry Library, deed of gift of her papers 2005 (Box 6)
  - Ojibwa -- Isle Royale, Michigan, letter and draft of paper by Timothy Cochrane entitled "Minong: An Ojibwas Sanctuary" 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - Runestone
    - Kehoe, Alice Beck, article by (Box 6)
    - Kensington, conference & related 2003 (Box 6)
    - Spirit Pond Runestones (Box 6)
    - Straight, Stephen, file, collected material (Box 6)
  - Schambach, Frank F., marginal notes on his article about Spiroan Culture 1992 (Box 7)
  - Sturm, John A. (Box 7)
  - Sugden, John. Biography of Tecumseh, notes on (Box 7)
  - Sugden, John. Correspondence 1995-2000 (Box 7)
  - Swarthmore College (Box 7)
  - Taylor, Sam Ad hoc, Indian Council (Box 7)
  - Transatlantic Encounters, course syllabus (Box 7)
  - Trygg Land Office, Ely, Minnesota, correspondence with J.W. Trygg 1964-1965 (Box 7)
  - U-D Mercy Indiana Law Center (Box 7)
  - University of Michigan Press (Box 7)
  - University of Michigan, Course Materials (Box 7)
  - University of Michigan -- clippings re Indian education 1978-1979 (Box 7)
  - University Presses of Florida, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - University Presses of Florida, Proposed history of colonial Florida (Box 7)
  - University of Oklahoma Press, HHT comments on manuscripts (Box 7)
  - Villaire, Louis A., report entitled "US Federally Recognized American Indian Tribal Nations in the States of Michigan Minnesota Wisconsin" (Box 7)
  - Wyandot reservations in Michigan and Ohio 1974 (Box 7)
  - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 7)
- Michigan Commission on Indian Affairs
  Michigan Commission on Indian Affairs: Tanner was a member of the Michigan Commission on Indian Affairs from 1966 to 1970 and secretary of the commission for a portion of that time. This series contains copies of correspondence and other documents relating to the commission.
  - Topical files 1967-1969
    - Arts and crafts (Box 8)
    - Athens, Michigan: status of Indian lands (Box 8)
    - Cameron, Herman E., director of Commission on Indian Affairs (carbon copies of outgoing correspondence), 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Comprehensive Health Screening Project (includes "A Health and Nutrition Study Among Michigan Indians" 1968), 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Economic development (Box 8)
    - Education (Box 8)
    - Fishing and hunting rights (Box 8)
    - Housing (Box 8)
    - Indian burial sites (Box 8)
    - Intertribal Council-Indian Community Action Program (Box 8)
    - U.S. Indian Claims Commission (Box 8)
    - University of Michigan. Proposed Community Development Program (Box 8)
  - Legislation-U.S. Congress (Box 8)
  - Programs of meetings (Box 8)
  - Michigan Indian Consultation 1967. A conference sponsored by the Division of Missions of the Michigan Council of Churches (Box 8)
  - Report: Indian Trust, Restricted and Tribal Lands in Michigan 1966 (Box 8)
  - Newsletter-Great Lakes Agency News, BIA 1965-1967 (Box 8)
  - Clippings: Indian Affairs Commission (Box 8)
  - Printed material (Box 8)
- U.S. v. Michigan (case of Indian claims against the state of Michigan on matters of fishing rights)
  U.S. v. Michigan: This case, argued in Grand Rapids, Mich., before U.S. District Judge Noel Fox in 1978 and 1979, led to a landmark decision affirming Native Americans' right to fish in the Great Lakes under 19th-century treaties. The plaintiffs, the United States with the Bay Mills Indian Community and Sault Ste. Marie Tribe, were suing the State of Michigan and Michigan Dept. of Natural Resources to enforce Native American fishing rights. Tanner was an expert witness for the plaintiffs in the case, and the collection contains depositions, testimony, briefs, and other documents from the case. Also included is a file of notes Tanner received from the Native American Rights Fund summarizing and commenting on a number of the depositions and other documents.
  - Depositions 1976-1978
    - Cleland, Charles E. December 13-14, 1976, 2 volumes (Box 8)
    - Clifton, James A. November 3-4, 1978, 2 volumes (Box 8)
    - Dominic, Waunetta March 29, 1977 (draft) (Box 8)
    - Kaiser, Ronald January 20, 1977 (Box 8)
    - LeBlanc, Arthur L. November 15, 1976 (Box 8)
    - Lumsden, Joseph K. November 15, 1976 (Box 8)
    - Mason, Philip P. December 15, 1976-April 7, 1977 (Volume 1) (Box 8)
    - Mason, Philip P. December 15, 1976-April 7, 1977 (Volumes 2-4) (Box 9)
    - Scott, John January 19, 1977 (Box 9)
    - Tanner, Helen Hornbeck January 10, 1977 (Box 9)
    - Tody, Wayne January 19, 1977 (Box 9)
    - Wright, Asa January 20, 1977 (Box 9)
  - Briefs 1977-1979
    - Brief in support of second motion of the state-defendants (State of Michigan) for partial summary judgment May 2, 1977 (Box 9)
    - Reply brief of the state-defendants (State of Michigan) in further support of the state's second motion for partial summary judgment June 30, 1977 (Box 9)
    - Joint pre-trial brief of the United States of America, Bay Mills Indian Community and the Sault Ste. Marie Tribe of Chippewa Indians January 30, 1978 (Box 9)
    - Michigan United Conservation Club's brief as amicus curiae January 30, 1978 (Box 9)
    - Trial brief, State of Michigan February 3, 1978 (Box 9)
    - Joint post-trial brief of the United States of America, Bay Mills Indian Community and the Sault Ste. Marie Tribe of Chippewa Indians January 5, 1979 (Box 9)
    - Joint post-trial brief of the United States of America, Bay Mills Indian Community and the Sault Ste. Marie Tribe of Chippewa Indians January 19, 1979 (Box 9)
    - Brief for defendants-appellants, State of Michigan September 14, 1979 (Box 9)
    - Brief of Michigan United Conservation Clubs, Inc., amicus curiae September 17, 1979 (Box 9)
  - Transcript of proceedings 1978-1979 (selected witnesses only)
    - Volume 1 February 27-28, 1978 (Plaintiffs' opening statements and Helen Hornbeck Tanner) (Box 9)
    - Volume 2 March 1-2, 1978 (Helen Hornbeck Tanner) (Box 9)
    - Volume 5 September 26-27, 1978 (Philip P. Mason) (Box 9)
    - Volume 6 September 29-October 2, 1978 (Philip P. Mason and Asa Wright) (Box 10)
    - Volume 7 October 3, 1978 (Asa Wright) (Box 10)
    - Volume 9 November 21-22, 1978 (James A. Clifton) (Box 10)
    - Volume 10 December 18-19, 1978 (Philip P. Mason) (Box 10)
    - Volume 11 February 2, 1979 (Closing arguments) (Box 10)
  - Other documents 1975-1979